Finding Aid for the Larry Gelbart Papers PASC.0022
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Projects
  - Television Projects
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 July 29 (Box 225, Folder 4)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2002 Aug 5 (Box 225, Folder 5)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 June (Box 225, Folder 6)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 June 15 (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 July (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 June-July (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2002 July 24 (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2002 July 9 (Box 226, Folder 5)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 June 11 (Box 226, Folder 6)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 Jan - May (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 June - July (Box 227, Folder 2)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2002 July 27 (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - ABC (The Corsairs), 2002 Apr - May (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 Aug - Sept (Box 229, Folder 5)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself (Folder 1 of 2), 2002 Aug - Sept (Box 229, Folder 6)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself (Folder 2 of 2), 2002 Aug - Sept (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 Oct (Box 230, Folder 2)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2002 Oct 1 (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 Aug (Box 230, Folder 4)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2002 Aug (Box 230, Folder 5)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 Aug (Box 230, Folder 6)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2002 Aug 23 (Box 231, Folder 1)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2002 Aug 5 (Box 231, Folder 2)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 Oct (Box 231, Folder 3)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, no date (Box 231, Folder 4)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2001 May - Aug (Box 232, Folder 5)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2001 Aug - 2002 Jan (Box 232, Folder 6)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, no date (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2001 June 20 (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2001 Aug - Oct (Box 233, Folder 3)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2001 June 20 (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2001 July 17 (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2001 July 23 (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2001 July 31 (Box 233, Folder 7)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2001 Sept 13 (Box 233, Folder 8)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2001 Apr - June (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2000 Oct - Feb 2001 (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, no date (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2001 Feb 2001 (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - Pancho Villa - historical timeline, no date (Box 234, Folder 5)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2000 Dec 27 (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2001 Jan 22 (Box 234, Folder 7)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2001 Jan 27 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2001 Jan 29 (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2001 Mar 15 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2001 June 20 (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2001 June 20 (Box 235, Folder 5)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2001 Mar 30 (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - Skin Game (The), 1998 Feb 17 (Box 237, Folder 5)
    - ABC Pilot, 2002 Jan - Feb (Box 237, Folder 6)
      Demigods and Mega-Moguls. See also The Corsairs.
    - ABC Pilot, 2002 Feb - Mar (Box 238, Folder 1)
    - ABC Pilot, 2002 Feb (Box 238, Folder 2)
    - ABC Pilot, 2002 Feb - Mar (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - ABC Pilot, 2002 Feb (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - ABC Pilot, 2002 Feb - Mar (Box 238, Folder 5)
    - ABC Pilot, 2002 Feb - Mar (Box 238, Folder 6)
    - ABC Pilot, 2001 Dec - 2002 Jan (Box 239, Folder 1)
      Appears to be Demigods and Mega-Moguls. See also The Corsairs.
    - ABC Pilot, 2001 Oct - 2002 Jan (Box 239, Folder 2)
    - ABC Pilot, 2002 Jan (Box 239, Folder 3)
    - ABC Pilot, 2002 Jan 12 (Box 239, Folder 4)
    - ABC Pilot, 2002 Feb 22 (Box 239, Folder 5)
    - ABC Pilot, 2002 Mar (Box 239, Folder 6)
    - ABC Pilot (Folder 1 of 2), 2002 Mar - Apr (Box 239, Folder 7)
    - ABC Pilot (Folder 2 of 2), 2002 Mar - Apr (Box 240, Folder 1)
    - ABC Pilot, 2002 Mar (Box 240, Folder 2)
    - ABC Pilot, 2002 Jan - Feb (Box 240, Folder 3)
    - Gonka (Folder 1 of 2), 1999 Nov - 2000 Feb (Box 247, Folder 4)
    - Gonka (Folder 2 of 2), 1999 Nov - 2000 Feb (Box 247, Folder 5)
    - MASH - articles, 2001 Mar - Apr (Box 263, Folder 4)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, no date (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself (Folder 2 of 3), 2003 June - July (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2003 July - Sept (Box 266, Folder 5)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself (Folder 1 of 2), 2003 July - Sept (Box 266, Folder 6)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself (Folder 2 of 2), 2003 July - Sept (Box 266, Folder 7)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself (Folder 1 of 2), 2002 Oct (Box 266, Folder 8)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself (Folder 2 of 2), 2002 Oct (Box 267, Folder 1)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 Oct - Nov (Box 267, Folder 2)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2003 Feb - June (Box 267, Folder 3)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself (Folder 1 of 2), 2003 Mar - Apr (Box 267, Folder 4)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself (Folder 2 of 2), 2003 Mar - Apr (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 Dec - 2003 Jan (Box 268, Folder 2)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 Nov - 2003 Feb (Box 268, Folder 3)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2003 Apr - May (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2003 July - Aug (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002 Nov - Dec (Box 268, Folder 6)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2003 Feb - Mar (Box 268, Folder 7)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2003 July - Oct (Box 269, Folder 1)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2003 July - Aug (Box 269, Folder 2)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself (Folder 1 of 3), 2003 June - July (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself (Folder 3 of 3), 2003 June - July (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2004 Feb - Mar (Box 271, Folder 5)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself - screenplay, 2002 Oct 21 (Box 274, Folder 2)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2004 May - July (Box 274, Folder 3)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2003 May - 2004 Jan (Box 274, Folder 4)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2002-2004 (Box 274, Folder 5)
    - Trip to Korea with Gene Reynolds - holograph notes, 1974 Mar (Box 290, Folder 3)
      May be related to MASH.
    - Voll-Edelstein, 2004 Sept - Oct (Box 303, Folder 7)
      Appears to be related to G-Man pilot pitch.
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2004 June - Aug (Box 309, Folder 2)
    - Rubber Room (The), 2005 Sept - Nov (Box 309, Folder 4)
    - Rubber Room (The), 2005 Mar - Oct (Box 309, Folder 5)
    - Analyst (The), 2005-2006 (Box 309, Folder 6)
      Also referred to as The A-List or Fincher Project.
    - Analyst (The), 2006 June (Box 309, Folder 7)
    - Analyst (The), 2006 Sept - Oct (Box 309, Folder 8)
    - Analyst (The) (Folder 1 of 2), 2006 June - Aug (Box 311, Folder 3)
    - Analyst (The) (Folder 2 of 2), 2006 June - Aug (Box 311, Folder 4)
    - Barbarians at the Gate - screenplay, 1992 Mar (Box 312, Folder 5)
    - ABC Pilot, 2002 Feb 22 (Box 312, Folder 6)
    - United States Art Cards, ca. 1980 (Box 313, Folder 1)
    - Weapons of Mass Distraction - screenplay, no date (Box 316, Folder 8)
    - Weapons of Mass Distraction - screenplay, no date (Box 316, Folder 9)
    - Network pilot episode, 1996 March 21 (Box 321, Folder 1)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2004 Feb - Sept (Box 322, Folder 3)
    - MASH, 1974 Apr 5 (Box 322, Folder 6)
    - Roger Bates, 2002-2004 (Box 323, Folder 1)
    - Step Wars, 2007 Aug (Box 323, Folder 2)
    - Step Wars, 2007 Feb - Aug (Box 323, Folder 3)
    - Ser. C SPAM, 2007 Mar - July (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - And Starring Pancho Villa as Himself, 2003 Sept 18 (Box 337, Folder 1)
    - 25 - Idea for a TV Series (Box 10, Folder 8)
      May 28, 1986. 2 pages and handwritten notes.
    - After M*A*S*H - ALL ABOUT CHRISTMAS EVE (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Scripts by Dennis Koenig. First draft (9/14/83), Second draft (9/15/83), Third draft (9/27/83), Final (10/4/83), Revised final (11/1/83)
    - After M*A*S*H - ANOTHER SATURDAY NIGHT (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Ken Levine, David Issacs, & Dennis Koenig. First draft (12/2/83), Revised first draft (12/9/83), Final draft (12/12/83), Revised final draft (1/3/84).
    - After M*A*S*H - BLADDER DAY SAINTS, THE (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Scripts by Everett Greenbaum and Elliott Reid. First draft (n.d.), Second draft (8/12/83), Revised second drafts [(8/12/83), (8/23/83), (8/24/83)], Final draft (8/29/83), Revised final (10/18/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - BY THE BOOK (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Scripts by Larry Balmagia. First draft (12/19/83), Second draft (1/1/84), Final draft (1/4/84), Revised final (1/10/84).
    - After M*A*S*H - CHIEF OF STAFF (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Scripts by G. Mitchell. First draft (10/13/83), Second revised draft (11/14/83), Final draft (11/15/83), Revised final (11/22/83). Annotations.
    - After M*A*S*H - C.Y.A. (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Scripts by J. Hirsch. First draft (10/20/83), Revised first draft (10/28/83), Final draft (11/03/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - FALLOUT (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart. Treatment (n.d.), First draft (10/10/83), Revised first draft (10/17/83), Final draft (11/18/83), Revised final draft (11/25/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - FEVER PITCH (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Scripts by Denis Koenig. First draft (01/06/84), Revised first draft (01/11/84), Final draft (01/12/84), Revised final draft (01/17/84).
    - After M*A*S*H - IT HAD TO BE YOU (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Scripts by Denis Koenig, Kevin Levine, David Isaacs. First draft (11/11/83), Second draft (11/17/83), Revised draft (11/21/83), Final draft (11/23/83), Revised final 12/08/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - KLINGER VS. KLINGER (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Scripts by Ken Levine and David Isaacs. First draft (05/24/83), second draft (06/08/83), revised second draft (06/13/83), revised final draft (08/03/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - LITTLE BROADCAST OF '53, THE (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Dennis Koenig. First draft (05/27/83), Second draft (07/09/83), Revised second (06/14/83), Final draft (06/17/83), Revised final (07/05/83), Second revised final (09/26/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - NIGHT SHIFT (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Scripts by Everett Greenbaum and Elliott Reid. First draft (n.d.), Second draft (07/01/83), Revised second (07/08/83), Final draft (07/12/83), Revised final (09/01/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - ODDS AND ENDS (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Scripts by Everett Greenbaum and Everett Reid. First draft (12/01/83), Revised first draft (12/06/83), Final draft (12/27/83), Revised final (12/15/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - PERSHING SQUARE (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Script by Larry Balmagia. First draft (11/18/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - SEPTEMBER OF '53 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart. First draft (06/01/83), Final draft (06/01/83), Revised final (06/22/83), Second revised final (07/26/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - SHALL WE DANCE? (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Scripts by Ken Levine and David Isaacs. First draft (07/28/83), final draft (08/01/83), revised final draft (08/29/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - SNAP, CRACKLE, PLOP (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Scripts by Dennis Koenig. First draft (06/27/83), revised final (07/06/83), second revised final (08/29/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - STAPH INSPECTION (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Scripts by Ken Levine and David Isaacs. First draft (09/12/83), second draft (09/22/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - SUNDAY, CRUDDY SUNDAY (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Scripts by Dennis Koenig. First drafts [(08/02/83) & (08/24/83)], second draft (08/17/83), revised final (10/03/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - THANKSGIVING OF '53 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Scripts by Dennis Koenig, Ken Levine and David Isaacs. First draft (06/24/83), Revised first draft (06/29/83), final draft (10/11/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - TOGETHER AGAIN (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart. First draft (07/05/83), Revised first (07/13/83), Final draft (07/08/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - UP AND DOWN PAYMENTS (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Scripts by Ken Levine and David Isaacs. First draft (01/05/83 [sic]), final draft (01/13/84), revised final (01/25/84).
    - After M*A*S*H - YOURS TRULY, MAX KLINGER (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Scripts by Ken Levine and David Isaacs. First draft (10/26/83), (11/02/83), (12/01/83).
    - After M*A*S*H - CBS Presskit for season 1983-84 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Highlights AfterM*A*S*H, Scarecrow and Mrs. King, Magnum PI, Alice, Jeffersons, Trapper John MD, Simon and Simon, et al.
    - After M*A*S*H - Copies of story boards for Main Titles (Box 5, Folder 6)
      8/15/83.
    - After M*A*S*H - Copies of Interior Set plans for show #2 (4 items). (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Copies of Interior Set plans for show #2 (4 items).
    - After M*A*S*H - Shooting schedule, 1983. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - After M*A*S*H - Call sheets for episodes (Box 5, Folder 9)
      10/27 and 12/14/83.
    - After M*A*S*H - Airdate scheduling materials 1983-84 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      With Fox Memoranda, directors schedules, and status reports from CBS.
    - After M*A*S*H - Correspondence - CBS and 20th Century Fox Memoranda (Box 5, Folder 11)
      June 1983.
    - After M*A*S*H - Story outlines, including memoranda, typed and handwritten notes (Box 9, Folder 1)
      1983-1984.
    - After M*A*S*H - Handwritten notes for various episodes (Box 9, Folder 2)
      No date.
    - After M*A*S*H - Organizational-administrative chart of personnel in a medical institution (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - After M*A*S*H - Miscellaneous notes and memoranda including 4 photographs of production personnel with Larry Gelbart. 11/16/83. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - After M*A*S*H - Clippings regarding the TV series from numerous sources. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - After M*A*S*H - Scripts, first drafts, handwritten and typed (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Summer 1983.
    - After M*A*S*H - Correspondence from viewers, Fall 1983. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - After M*A*S*H - Transcripts of interviews with Veterans Administration personnel, doctors, nurses, clergy, etc. 16 folders. (Box 177)
      1983
    - After M*A*S*H - Transcripts of interviews with personnel from the Veterans Administration. (Box 178)
      1983. 6 folders.
    - After M*A*S*H - Transcripts of interviews with personnel of the Veterans Administration (Box 179)
      1983. 7 folders.
    - ART CARNEY SHOW (THE) - Sketches for an Art Carney special (Box 80, Folder 11)
      No date. 6 items.
    - ART CARNEY SHOW (THE) - SMALL WORLD, ISN'T IT (Box 87, Folder 1)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Shelley Keller. Final draft, 09/28/59, 60 p. - Draft, n.d., annotated, 60 p.
    - ART CARNEY SHOW (THE) - VERY IMPORTANT PEOPLE (Box 87, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller. Final draft, "as aired," 11/27/59, annotated, 63 p. - Final draft, 11/27, 80 p. - First draft, 11/13/59, 66 p.
    - ART CARNEY SHOW (THE) - BEST OF ANYTHING, THE (Box 87, Folder 3)
      Script by Sheldon Keller and Larry Gelbart. First draft, 02/18/60, 62 p.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 154, Folder 8)
      Screenplay, pages 2 - 137, annotated by L.G. Another draft, pages 2 - 106, annotated by L.G.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 154, Folder 9)
      Screenplay. August 9 1990, 105 pages.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 156, Folder 1)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart, first draft, August 24 1990, annotated, 135 pages.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 156, Folder 2)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart, first draft, September 1, 1990, 135 pages. Different draft, September 1, 1990, 134p.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 156, Folder 3)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart, first draft, September 10, 1990, annotated, 135 pages.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 156, Folder 4)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart, first draft, September 12, 1990, 137 pages.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 156, Folder 5)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart, second draft, December 12, 1990, 135 pages.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 156, Folder 6)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart, March 13 1992, 115 pages. - Revised pages, same date.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 156, Folder 7)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart, revised draft, March 19, 1991, annotated, 118 pages.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 157, Folder 1)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart, revised draft, November 1991-March 1992. 205 scenes/shots.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 157, Folder 2)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart. Draft with laser printer cover sheet, April 7 1991, 43p. Another draft, April 5, 1991, 41p.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 157, Folder 3)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Revised draft, with laser printer cover sheet, annotated, April 10, 1991, 139 p. Clipping from L.A. Times "TV Times," March 14-20, 1993.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 157, Folder 4)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Fourth Draft, April 22 1991, heavily annotated, 133 p.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 157, Folder 5)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Revised draft, October 28 1991, 106 p.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 157, Folder 6)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Revised draft, November 1 1991, 112 p.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 157, Folder 7)
      Screenplay. Revised, 01/17/92, 111 p. [Pages with revisions are noted on title page.]
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 157, Folder 8)
      Revisions of the opening scene, Dated June 23 (8 pages), 24 (12 pages), 25 (16 pages), 27, 1990 (22 pages). Handwritten notes, 2p. Rehearsal schedule, 1p. Revised script pages, March 13 and 27, 1992, 2p.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 157, Folder 9)
      Revised sections, dated July 21, 29, 31 1992, and September 17 1992. Scene breakdown, April 22, 1991, 11p. Outline of script, October 20, 1990, 3p. Correspondence.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 158, Folder 1)
      Screenplay. Incomplete script, revision pages, 9/18/92. Handwritten notes, 9/20/92, 4p. Misc. revised script pages. Correspondence re: network standards.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 158, Folder 2)
      Oneline Schedule, 18 pages, 18 March 1992 and Crew List, 7 pages, March 21, 1992.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 158, Folder 3)
      Network standards acceptability report with suggested revisions, September 15, 1992.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 158, Folder 4)
      Research materials: Production book including: Comments on revisions, Research for Major Wall Street Events, Timetable, Major Players, and Story Breakdown. June, 1990.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 158, Folder 5)
      Research packet for production. Annotated. No date.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 158, Folder 6)
      Research packet for production. Character studies and articles on major business personalities. Annotated. No date.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 158, Folder 7)
      Research packet: Correspondence regarding rewrites, Current Research, Reviews, Ross Johnson background and RJR Nabisco background. February, 1990. Annotated. Handwritten notes, 2p.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 158, Folder 8)
      Correspondence, 1992. Regarding casting and other production concerns.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 158, Folder 9)
      Clippings, May 1992. Regarding filming. Invitation to Los Angeles premiere screening at Director's Guild, 3/9/93.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 159, Folder 1)
      Story breakdowns, n.d. and 2/22/90 (2 items). Handwritten notes, 5p. Correspondence. Research materials. Clippings re: "Barbarians at the Gate," Michael Milken, RJR Nabisco, Ivan Boesky, and other related topics.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 159, Folder 2)
      Articles and reviews. 1992-3. (xerox copies).
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 159, Folder 3)
      Reviews of the production, 1992-3. (Clippings and xerox copies).
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 159, Folder 4)
      Miscellaneous: Barbarians At the Gate Dinner Invitation. - Emmy nomination certificate (1993). - Acceptance speeches (6) with annotations.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 159, Folder 5)
      Transcript of interview of Larry Gelbart by Maggie Schmidt, with corrections and annotations by Larry Gelbart. - Cover letter explaining corrections, November 17, 1992.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 159, Folder 6)
      Congratulatory letters to Larry Gelbart regarding ACE and Golden Awards, January 1994. Approx. 50 items.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 159, Folder 7)
      Publicity, letters, clippings re the 15th Annual National Cable ACE Awards, November 1993. - Letters re the First Annual American Television Awards, May 1993.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 160, Folder 1)
      Emmy Awards, 1993: Letters (2) of congratulations. - 3 B/W photos of Larry Gelbart w/people. - Emmy Tickets (4). - HBO Emmy booklet. - Emmys Seating list. - Emmy Program.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 160, Folder 2)
      Unbound published manuscript. Marked "Keep Hearing Dodger Games -- Election Stuff." Annotated, no date for annotations.
    - BARBARIANS AT THE GATE (HBO, 1992) (Box 160, Folder 3)
      Book: "Barbarians at the Gate: The Fall of RJR Nabsico," by Bryan Burrough and John Helyar, Harper and Row, 1990. Annotated by Larry Gelbart.
    - BARBRA STREISAND AND OTHER MUSICAL INSTRUMENTS (Box 155, Folder 3)
      Script, no author, July 1973, Artists: Ray Charles and Raelets. Incl. shooting and rehearsal schedules, 72 pages. - Typed drafts (4) of monologue for Barbra Streisand, one annotated [by L.G.].
    - CAESAR'S HOUR - Show #31-32 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Scripts by Mel Tolkin, Larry Gelbart, Mel Brooks, et al. 9/26/55 - 10/03/55.
    - CAESAR'S HOUR - Show #33-34 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Scripts by Mel Tolkin, Larry Gelbart, Mel Brooks, et al. 10/10/55 - 10/24/55.
    - CAESAR'S HOUR - Show #35-36 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Scripts by Mel Tolkin, Larry Gelbart, Mel Brooks. 10/31/55 - 11/07/55.
    - CAESAR'S HOUR - Show #38-39 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Mel Tolkin, Larry Gelbart, Mel Brooks. 11/28/55 - 12/5/55.
    - CAESAR'S HOUR - Show #40-41 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      Scripts by Mel Tolkin, Larry Gelbart, Mel Brooks, et al. 12/19/55 - 12/26/55.